(Amy:)Okay, your turn.
(Amy:)Hmm. Seal,
(Amy:)hagfish...
(Amy:)SpongeBob SquarePants.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'd befriend SpongeBob
but he's not real,
(Sheldon:)so I can't do that, can I?
(Amy:)But you can pal around
with a hagfish?
(Sheldon:)Hey, let's not pull
at that thread.
(Howard:)Okay. I'll
fight SpongeBob,
(Sheldon:)because he's so friendly we'll
just end up tickling each other.
(Sheldon:)Um, I'll befriend the seal,
(Sheldon:)because he's trainable,
which is the problem
(Sheldon:)I'm having with my
current friends.
(Sheldon:)Which means I'll have
to eat the hagfish.
(Amy:)Isn't that gross?
I mean, a hagfish can produce
(Amy:)enough mucus to fill a bucket
in a minute.
(Sheldon:)I know. It makes its own gravy...
it'll slide right down.
(Amy:)I miss this.
(Sheldon:)How can you miss a game you've
never played before, silly?
(Amy:)I guess sometimes I'm silly.